http://www.copperriverseafood.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Loading... Please wait...
100% USA Owned & Operated
Taste the Wild, Taste the Difference!
Careers
Senior AccountantDriver IMaintenance Technician IChief Engineer - CRS Operations2020 Recruitment ScheduleOnline ApplicationVideosFirst Copper River Salmon of 2015
Recipes
Salmon RecipesHalibut RecipesCrab RecipesScallop RecipesRockfish RecipesCod Recipes
Health Benefits
COVID-19 Safety
Wild Alaska Seafood
Check Out What's NEW!
6oz Halibut Portions
Native Style Smoked Salmon
Keta Salmon Ikura (Roe)
Coho Salmon Ikura (Roe)
Pink
Salmon Ikura (Roe)
Rockfish
Alaska Golden King Crab
Skinless Sockeye Salmon Portions - 6oz
Skinless Sockeye Salmon Filets
Alaskan Weekend Sampler
Alaska Halibut Bits
Alaska Halibut Kickers
Wild Alaska King Salmon
Halibut Burger
Sable Fish (Black Cod)
Wild Alaska Smoked Sockeye Salmon
Manager's Special
Wild Alaska Smoked Sockeye Salmon
Frozen Samplers
Alaskan Weekend Sampler
Northern Lights Seafood Duo
Copper River Salmon
Copper River King Salmon
Copper River Sockeye Salmon
Copper River Coho Salmon
Wild-Caught Seafood
Ikura (roe)
Fresh Alaska King Salmon
Fresh Alaska Sockeye Salmon
Fresh Alaska Halibut
Red King Crab
Golden King Crab
King Crab
Native Style Smoked Salmon
Wild Alaska Ling Cod
Sort
Bulk - Best Value on Shipping!
Price: Low to High
Price: High to Low
No Refrigeration Needed
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Copper River Seafoods, Inc. (COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC.) has created this privacy statement to declare its forthright commitment to the privacy of its customers and users of this website. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. uses, maintains and discloses information collected from its customers and users of its websites.
The Information We Collect
COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. may request or collect personal information from online users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products, subscribing to newsletters and other instances where users are invited to volunteer such information.
The data we collect is information that identifies you personally, such as: name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone numbers, website URLs, credit card information and other billing information. This information is used for billing and service purposes for the products or services you sign up for. With this information, you can expect to receive billing notices, order confirmations and important service related correspondence. If you do not wish to provide us with this information or do not wish to receive communications from us, please opt not to sign-up.
COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. may also collect information about how users access the website using a tracking ID unique to each user through the use of cookies. This information is for internal use only and does not personally identify you in any way.
Cookies may also be used by third party affiliate sites to verify any purchase you might make so that they make rightfully earn their duly earned commissions. The affiliate tracking cookies only tag your purchase from their referral site to ours and do not personally identify you in any way to the third party. At no point in time will any third party obtain any personally identifiable information.
Information collected on our site is only collected by us and no one else.
So What Are Cookies?
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computer’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Your browser’s help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Session ID cookies may be used by COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. to track user preferences while the user is visiting the website. They also help to minimize load times and save on server processing. Persistent cookies may be used by COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. to store whether, for example, you want your password remembered or not, and other information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site
Log Files
Like most standard websites, we use log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. None of the information stored in the log files is linked to personally identifiable information.
How We Use This Information
COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. may use the personally identifiable information collected by COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. to contact customers regarding products and services offered by COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. and, to the extent the user has agreed to it, by its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. We may also use this information for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of our website services, marketing, advertising and sales efforts. COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. will not in any way share this information with a third party either for free or by selling it, unless you specifically authorize such disclosures.
You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. No information will be collected or provided to third parties without your prior knowledge.
Disclosure of Information
COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to investors and potential partners. In such cases, only statistical information will be disclosed and personally identifiable data will be kept strictly confidential. In case COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. is sold, the information collected from users may be transferred to the new owners.
COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. may from time to time engage third parties, including its own subsidiaries and affiliated companies, to preserve, analyze or otherwise store or manipulate data received by COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. from its customers. In all such cases, third party service providers will be required to treat all such data with the same degree of care as COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. and they will be prohibited from disclosing such data to any other person or party, except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy.
We use various credit card processing companies to bill you for our products and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. No other third party services are used to provide the services you purchase from us, thus no personally identifiable information is provided beyond our service.
Special Offers and Updates
Our customers and users will occasionally receive newsletters or e-mails with information on products, services, or special offers. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. gives the opportunity to opt-out from receiving these types of communications.
If do not wish to receive our newsletter, promotional communications or any other non-service related communication, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at info@copperriverseafoods.com or you may contact us at 907.522.7806.
On some occasions, it may be necessary to send out service-related announcements. In most cases, users may not opt-out of these communications. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. You may deactivate your account by emailing us at info@copperriverseafoods.com
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary and required to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, subpoena or other legal process served on COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC..
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
The COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC. Privacy Policy as described herein applies solely to information collected by COPPER RIVER SEAFOODS, INC..
Changes to this Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page or within your account profile.
Shop Wild Alaska Seafood
Holiday
Gift Boxes
Stocking Stuffers
Gift Certificates
Copper River Salmon
Copper River King Salmon
Copper River Sockeye Salmon
Join Us!
© 2020 Copper River Seafoods, Inc.
1118 E 5th Avenue, Anchorage, AK 99501
Contact Us
Map Locations
